Hello everyone, I'm Aristo Yamano and Momoka Yamano of Nyari Call Joy!
Today, Momoka and I went shopping at Cosm Kitchen!
Today, we are going to buy some items that we use in our daily life, and we also hope to find some new good items.
We hope you enjoy reading this article!
Well, let's get started.
Okay, I'm off.
This is amazing. There are so many.
I've never seen it before.
Is there anything you want?
I did some preliminary research.
I wanted to get a primer, a pack, and either a powder or a lipstick.
That's nice. Skin care products are good. But I'm also looking for a face pack, powder, or lipstick.
But I'm also interested in a face pack.
I heard that this Famu pack is really good.
I'm curious about it.
There are so many different kinds.
It's a little out of my price range.
But I'm interested in this one.
Before a concert...
Before an important day like that.
I want this.
I want one of these, don't you?
There are so many kinds.
There's also a firming type.
It'll get rid of pores and stuff.
That might be nice.
You like it? I like this one.
I like this one better.
Each one.
Do you want different kinds?
We'll have the same kind.
Here you go.
It's amazing. Let's use them for the big day.
Hey.
Let's go this way.
I was watching something.
You were looking?
Maybe it's this primer.
Wait, I want this.
This?
Yeah.
I think I might want this one.
Maybe this lavender-beige primer.
It's nice.
I think I'll buy this one.
Buy it. Buy it.
Buy it.
I also like this etobos, I usually like this brand.
I just thought this eyeshadow was cute.
Looks good on you.
Cute.
I'm thinking of buying this one because of the pretty blue-ish color.
It'll definitely look good on you.
Really? Do you think it'll look good on me? It's sparkly and I think I can use it for live performances, so it'll definitely be popular. It's so sparkly, I think it'll look good at a live performance.
I'm sure it'll go well at live shows.
Do you want to buy it?
I'll buy it.
Well, Alice, you have a lot to choose from.
I'm really interested in this powder.
It's mineral-based, so I'm thinking it'll be good for my skin.
I heard it comes in two colors.
Pink.
Isn't pink good?
Pink is definitely good.
Are you a Bourbé girl, Alice?
Yes, I'm a Bourbe.
Okay, the pink one of the powder.
Would you like to buy the pink one?
Pink veil.
I'd like to buy this one.
Yes, ma'am.
I couldn't figure out how much.
How much is it going for now? I'm thinking about 4,600 yen.
I'm about three. I'm at...
I'll buy a pack for 3,000 yen and this for 4,000 yen.
I'm thinking of buying an eye shadow. I'm thinking of getting eyeshadows, and then I'll go, right?
Yeah, probably.
Wait a minute. Can I reconsider? Are you sure?
But I'm starting to think that I have a lot of eyeshadows, and I was thinking that maybe I'd be better off with a serum or something.
But when I looked at the official website, this one was really high on the list.
This is a booster. I might want to get one.
I want all of them! Oh, man!
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do. My budget is too tight.
I spend money on cosmetics so quickly, don't I?
I think I'm going to go with this one.
What's the difference?
It's a big bottle, so I'll just try it out and go with this one.
TONE Booster Serum, I'll go with this one.
That's nice.
Yay get it!
Get, get, get!
Wait, I...
I love purification.
This is so good!
I've been using OISE's purifying spray thingy for a while now.
I feel like I'm shaking it.
Is this New York?
Is it made in New York? Is it New York wood?
I'm really curious about this.
There are so many kinds.
Power Energy?
This is the salt of God.
I'm kind of curious about this one, so I'm gonna buy this one.
I'm kind of buying this one.
I think I might be buying too much.
Is it good? Still good?
Yeah, I think so.
I can't do the math.
So, Alice, you don't buy absolutes anymore?
Fine-tuning.
Let's buy the fine type.
I'd like to buy one.
I heard there's a waiting list.
It's so popular.
It's amazing!
Vanilla.
It's a lipstick.
It's Dorami.
He's so cute.
It's got some color on it.
It's got color.
It's citrusy.
I'll do both.
This one.
But, you know, the original producer...
I don't think it's a coincidence that it smells so good.
I really love the smell of Lipburn.
I'm really thinking about getting a dry-on.
I'm thinking about buying the dry-only one because I think it's budget-friendly.
I'd like to buy this scent.
I'd like to buy this one. Dorami.
Yes, the fragrance is...
The scent is different?
Yes, it's different.
It's definitely different, and it doesn't even have a color.
It's nice. Okay, I'll go with that one.
Yes, I do.
Yay.
I think this is about right.
I think it's about right.
I think I'm a little over.
But I had to decide between eye shadow and foundation.
I see.
Can I swatch this a little bit?
I think it's good.
Oh, wait, it's cute!
Oh, it's so lame!
It's so cute.
It's so cute, I'm shaking.
Oh, my God.
This is gonna look so good on you.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Okay, I'll go with this one.
I'll go with the eyeshadow.
Okay, bye.
I'll go with this one.
Decided.
I think this is about right.
I hope so.
I'm done shopping.
I would like to introduce the items I bought now.
Okay, I'd like to introduce them alternately from Momoku.
Then I'll return this one to you.
The first one, then, is this one that I bought with Arisu.
Dream Glow Mask by Famu.
I went for the clear and flawless type.
This was a pack I've been eyeing for a long time already, so I'm going to use it on the night of the big day.
Great.
Okay, Alice.
Yes, me too, then.
One more time through.
I bought the matching Famu this one, the tightening booster one.
Great. Let's get rid of the tightening pores.
Yes, I'll use this one too on the big day.
Okay, next is this tone booster serum called M.
This is a serum.
I thought I'd be very happy to get a product that I was really interested in because of its high ranking on the official website, so I bought it.
It's true. I often wear makeup for a long time.
I hope I can use it at live performances.
Yay.
Okay, here's me next.
It's an eyeshadow in the color French Fig from Eto Boss Mineral Classy Shadow Eye!
I was having a hard time deciding on this one.
Alice gave me a nudge and said it would look good on Momoka, so I bought it.
I'm so happy! I think I'll use this one at the show too.
Then I bought this lavender-beige primer from etobos!
It's nice.
It's very pink.
I bought a pink primer today.
I bought a pink primer.
Yes, it's nice.
I'm the last one.
Okay, I'll finish up.
Purifying Salt Pro.
What does it say? Salt of the gods?
The Abyss.
Abyss.
I don't know how to read it.
I bought the one called Power Energy.
It's something you put in the bathtub.
I like this brand "Oise-san" very much.
I also use their "Okiyami Spray" and other products.
I trust this brand, so I bought it!
That's all!
I have only one product.
It is a sheer lip balm from THE PRODUCT.
This one is a collaboration with Doraemon,
I love the smell of it.
My favorite?
I liked it, so I bought it.
It's nice. Let's make it plump.
Let's make it plump.
That's all.
We both bought four items.
I'm glad.
Yes, there were a lot of products I hadn't seen before.
You know a lot about Peach Blossom and so on.
Not at all.
That was fun.
But it was really fun to be on the bus surrounded by my favorite cosmetics.
It was so much fun to be able to take pictures with Alice and do the shopping!
I'd love to do it again.
I would love to do it again.
If it's popular, I'd like to shoot a lot of cosmetics projects like this.
If you write in the comments section what kind of beauty videos you would like to see, please let me know.
If you make a request, we'll shoot it!
We'd love to hear from you!
We're looking forward to your comments!
If you liked this video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel!
That's all for now, Nearly Call Join!
Bye bye.